<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HomeScreen</string>
    <string name="magnus_description">Description: In an age long lost to legend and myth.

In an age where humans had still yet to establish a system of writing.

It’s said that there existed a Magus in a country named Scarlet.

It’s said that he imparted knowledge concerning language and writing, taught how to cultivate the lands, instructed the ways of raising animals, and brought about the gift—nay, the magic of fire.

It’s said that he was a dauntless youth, a dragon clad in scarlet red scales, a person worshiped far and wide.

It’s said that this man was the God of Civilization.

Yet strangely, his name had been virtually wiped from the records.

Therefore, he was simply referred to as—

—The Magus of Genesis.</string>
    <string name="magnus_chap1">A Dragon’s Breath 竜の吐息
Each time I exhale, a blessing escapes.
… Literally.

The next day.

“Morning…”

Nina rubbed the sleepiness from her eyes as she spoke, her mouth wide open due to yawning.

“Good morning.”

Still trying not to look at her butt-naked body to my utmost, I greeted her back.

“Still tired… you were so noisy last night…”

“Sorry.”

Complaining, she held out her hands and the trees shook as they inclined their leaves toward her, having the dew on them drip into her palms. Once Nina was done washing her face, wind blew away the remaining water on her face. Next, the silk she’d tossed over on the tree branch floated over to Nina, wrapped around her body, and turned into clothing.

As ever, magic is a magnificent thing.

I decided to call her race elves for convenience’s sake. It’s just for convenience because, be it their abilities, lifestyle, or physical characteristics, they differed heavily from the design laid out by the great 20th century novelist named Tolkien—they even differed from the variety of elves that existed within Norse mythology, the álfr.

I guess it might have been more accurate to call them dryads or nymphs, but there’s no reason I have to match it with Earth’s mythology either way. She lives in this world and is an existence of this world, after all.

“So what was that think you were on about? An academy?”

“Yeah. I’d like you to help me build one, Nina.”

Typing up her golden hair with blades of grass, she asked me about what I brought up last night.

I nodded—her cooperation was imperative for the academy I pictured.

“I don’t really mind.”

Elves seemed to live very monotonous lives.

That’s also the reason she was even associating with a strange dragon like me. I also think that it’s because it meant that she’d be able to live without having to work, though.

“What is that academy thing, anyway?”

“An academy is a place you live at for a long time, somewhere to teach youths about the world. Your parents taught you about the world, right?”

“Well… yeah.”

Tilting her head to the side as she recalled her past, she nodded.

“Humans are a race much younger than yours. When it comes to what they need to survive, they know next to nothing. I will build a magic academy and teach them magic.”

“… Magic?”

Magic was another world that didn’t exist in Elvish. Nina repeated the word I’d spoken in Japanese back to me.

“Nina, you know how you manipulate trees? That’s magic.”

“Eh—”

Her eyes opened wide in surprise.

“Teach, you say… how?”

She looked as though she had no idea how that could be done.

“Nina, how do you do it?”

“How…?”

Saying that, Nina looked over to a tree and extended her arm toward it.

The tree rustled and moved to place a branch on her palm almost exactly like she’d given it a command to [Shake] like one might give to a dog.

“Like that.”

Nina knit her brows, troubled. She didn’t have any further explanation to give me.

I see. I guess that to her, moving trees is like moving her own limbs.

“I mean, you’d be stumped if I asked you how you breathe fire, right?”

“Ah. So that’s magic, too, then.”

It’s rather obvious now that I think about it. Breathing is something done to take in oxygen, how would I be able to do that if my lungs were filled with fire? It’s simply impossible. So, obviously, that has to be magic as well.

But she is right, though. I wouldn’t be able to explain to her how I’m breathing out fire. It’s just like breathing normally to me. I myself don’t even feel the heat from it. That fact often causes me to forget that I breathe fire, though.

“Nina. Can you move your arms without moving trees along with them?”

“Yup.”

When I thought of something and gave asking Nina about it a shot, she quickly held up her arm. As expected, it appears as her action itself isn’t the requirement for it. In other words, I should be able to both breathe fire and not breathe fire.

“Could you try moving them this time?”

“Sure.”

This time, Nina just looked at them without changing her stance.

A tree branch squirmed, shaking up and down.

“What did you do different?”

“Umm, I… imagined it?”

So it’s all about the image, is it? Let’s give it a shot.

I closed my eyes and imagined myself from before I reincarnated, back when I still had the body of a human.

A body standing on two legs. A back with no wings. An upright neck.

I breathed in slowly, the air filling me lunged.

Then, keeping that image in my head… I breathed out.

“Kyaah!? What’re you doing!?”

“Ah! Sorry!”

Panicking, I beat out the flames that had started to spread into the trees.

It seems like doing it right won’t be easy.

＊　＊　＊
The firewood crackled, making popping noises.

“So you do eat meat, huh…”

“Hmm? Did you say something?”

Nina was digging in to some roasted deer meat, enjoying its flavor immensely.

“You don’t think that it’s pitiful or anything, do you?”

“Huh?”

Hearing my question, Nina tilted her head to the side and replied like I’d just said something weird.

“Ah, sorry. It’s nothing.”

I guess that’s the normal response? That kind of thinking is something that only more plentiful societies would have. But it’s really surreal seeing a dainty elf chow down ravenously on a hunk of roasted meat.

I say that, but I’m even worse in terms of sophistication.

Having a dragon’s body even changed my sense of taste, so things taste delicious even if they’re raw.

Juices ooze out of the meat when it gets burned by the flames in my throat. It’s extremely delicious.</string>
    <string name="magnus_chap2">His First Pupil 初めての生徒
That’s one small step for man,

—Neil Armstrong

“Welcome, back. Mentor.”

Her face full of smiles, Ai ran over to me when I landed at the forest’s entrance.

“I’m back. But Ai, you shouldn’t leave the forest.”

“You didn’t say that she couldn’t greet you. And besides, she’s still barely in the forest, it’s alright.”

Nina popped up from behind Ai, sighing.

This world was filled with dangerous animals.

Although there weren’t many fierce beasts like the Armored Bear, there are many animals that could be dangerous to a young girl like Ai in both the forest and the grasslands outside of it.

They’d be able to stay out of danger so long as they’re in the forest because of what Nina can do, but I get worried when they’re at the forest’s boundary like right now. But although I get worried—

“Mentor… did I, do bad…?”

“No, you did well. Thank you for coming to greet me.”

I just couldn’t find it in me to berate Ai after seeing her get so dejected like that and forgave her.

… Which caused her face to light up into a smile as she clung to my muzzle.

“What was this kind of thing called again… a [Doting Dummy]?”

Nina snorted as she poked fun at me.

I only said that term one time… good job on remembering.

What she spoke with and what I’ve been teaching Ai wasn’t Elvish, but Japanese.

I was a bit troubled over which language I wanted to teach Ai.

If I went with Japanese, I’d have to teach it to Nina as well.

But I decided on teaching her Japanese even after taking the disadvantages into consideration.

I mean, there is a remarkable difference in the amount of vocabulary between Elvish and Japanese.

Elvish uses simple ways to express things and is staggeringly restrictive for more complex matters.

For example, there isn’t a word that means [Word]. There aren’t even any other languages, after all. It has neither [Magic] nor [Academy] and even lacks words for [Elf] and [Human].

I wouldn’t be able to run an academy with that many limitations.

I’d just been substituting Japanese words into Elvish for words it didn’t have, but I felt that it would be faster to just have her to learn Japanese itself.

Which is why I taught the two of them Japanese. They still falter a bit when they speak, but it’s gotten to the point that they’re able to have everyday conversations without being too troubled. It didn’t happen in a simple few days like it did when I learned Japanese, but it has been several months since I first began teaching them. They’re both astoundingly fast learners.

“Nina-san. Mentor, not a dummy.”

Ai started puffing out her cheeks in anger.

The girl who’d trembled in fear at the mere sight of me had grown very attached to me these past few months.

“No, I mean that he’s wonderful at that.”

Meanwhile, Nina was the same as ever.

It feels like she’s grown attached to me as well, though.

“What do you mean, that?”

“Alright you two, stop quarreling. How about we have some lunch?”

Saying that, I held up the fish basket I was carrying on my foreleg.

Although dragon forefeet are surprisingly dexterous, it’s not to the point of being able to weave baskets.

The basket was made by Nina.

“Let’s head home.”

Yes, home. The era of us living with tree boughs as our roof has long since come to an end.

It isn’t much to look at, but we have a house.

It’s not far off from the forest’s entrance and was surrounded by some sporadically placed trees.

We made the house out of wood, so it’s simple, yet sturdy. It doesn’t even break when I enter it either.

Well, although it is large enough that I’m able to move around inside it without being inconvenienced, I probably won’t be able to fit sooner or later, given how mother’s size makes it appear that dragons continue growing forever and how I’m already larger than a horse.

But that’s not all. It’s all made from wood, but we have furniture, too.

Nina took out an unglazed pot as Ai arranged our dishes on the table.

What a civilized sight this is.

It’s an incredible leap in progress compared to the time we were eating roasted dear outside.

“Alright, roast it.”

“Yeah.”

I blew a few minor flames out onto the fishes she’d stuck sticks through to skewer them. I’d caused quite a lot of our meats to burn into nothing at first and had even almost burned down our house at one point, but I’ve since gotten used to doing it.

Grilled in the blink of an eye, a fragrant smell spread through the house.

That done, Nina started Nina sprinkled some salt that she’d gotten from the pot onto it all.

“Now then.”

“Well.”

“Yeah.”

“”” Time to eat! “””

Our voices overlapped.

Picking up a skewer with the tips of my toes and placing it on my tongue, I threw it back into my mouth and ate it all at once. An irresistible umami flavor spread through my mouth as the grease and salt mixed together.

“It’s so good!”

“Hey! Be careful!”

“Whoops, excuse me.”

Nina shouted at the sight of me accidentally flaming at the mouth.

I’ve gotten to the point I can just about control the flames, but they sometimes make their way out when I get excited.

“It just means the fish you salted was so tasty that my fire wanted some too.”





“How irresponsible, really now.”</string>
</resources>